

#### Personal

Name Priyadarshini Rajmohan

Address Plot no:35,VGN Oval Garden, Athipetu, Ambattur, 600058 Chennai

Phone number 9524277129

Email priyasathyasai@gmail.com

Website https://priyadarshinisai.github.io/PriyadarshiniRajmohan/

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/priyadarshini-rajmohan-b26b23b0



## Summary

Passionate person with skills in IT. Worked on over 7 web application projects and provided technical support to end users, leveraging extensive expertise to manage issue identification.

About 5 years of experience in Java, Spring and SQL and in front end technologies like Angular 8,12, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Typescript and PrimeNG. Looking forward to work with leading software companies to give my complete contribution with my experience for active participation and to lead the team, meeting the target on time and achieving success for walk of my life and for the company.



# Work experience

Jul 2021 - Present **Technology Analyst** 

Infosys, Chennai

- Responsible for creating efficient designs and developing User Interaction screens using HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript and Angular 8,12.
- Designing user interactions on web pages and developing APIs to extract clusters of data for processing the participation of VINs in each country for recall management.
- Developed translation for 30 languages using ngx-translate library.
- Experience with creating custom directives, decorators, and services to interface with restful services.
- Implemented Angular Router to enable navigation from one view to the next as customer performs application tasks.
- Implemented HTTP requests using RxJS, Observable library to handle multiple values over time.
- Build reusable Typescript components and services to consume REST APIs with component-based architecture.
- Hold team meetings to manage expectations and make team changes.
- Worked extensively in Agile Development process.
- Coordinated with multiple vendors from geographically distributed teams for the successful development, testing and deployment of a projects.

**Senior System Engineer** Jul 2020 - Jun 2021

Infosys, Chennai

- Designed rich prototypes and Applications using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript and Angular 8,12.
- Involved in writing application-level code to interact with APIs, Web Services using JSON.
- Created reusable components, templates and style sheets based on UI standards and guidelines.
- Performed functional tasks using specifications and wireframes.
- Implemented Angular Router to enable navigation from one view to the next as customer performs application tasks.
- Implemented HTTP requests using RxJS, Observable library to handle multiple values over time.
- Worked with Jasmine for unit testing angular modules.
- Designed and developed the application using Agile Scrum methodology by breaking down the project into several sprints
- Coordinate with multiple geographically dispersed team providers to successfully develop and test projects.

**System Engineer** Jul 2018 - Jul 2020

Infosys, Chennai

- Deliver software programs on time.
- Performed automation process to reduce work time of 12 hours per month and process data more effectively using Java.
- Performing impact analysis and completing the sprint tasks on time with quality.
- Engaged in various root cause analysis of chronic issues arising at L1/L2 level by coordinating with Problem Management to reduce the number of severity 1 and severity 2 incidents.
- · Always challenge situations and provide ideas to improve workflow and maintain code structure and guidelines.
- Performing proper unit testing and integration testing.
- Analyzing the error trends aimed at reducing downtime.
- Monitoring, recoding and responding to requests for support.

**System Engineer Trainee** Jan 2018 - May 2018

Infosys, Mysore

- Trained in Java, Angular and Bootstrap.
- Developed blog search engine for sports category that retrieves the required content for the search from blogs stored using TF IDF technique.
- Performing analysis and completing the project on time with quality.



## Education and Qualifications

## **B.E (Computer Science and Engineering)**

Jun 2014 - Apr 2018

Kongu Engineering College, Perundurai

Graduated with 92% CGPA with First class distinction



# Skills

### Programming skills, Team lead, Problem Solving

Experienced

#### Analytical Ability, Critical Thinking, Collaboration

Experienced



## ■ Technical Expertise

Front-End Frameworks: Angular 8,12, PrimeNG Web Technologies: HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, SASS

Programming Languages: Java/J2EE, Spring, RDBMS, JavaScript, Typescript

Version Control :Git



#### ■ Awards

## • Insta Awards-Certificate of Appreciation:

Awarded for being flexible and dedicated resource. For gaining the customer confidence in short span of time and also for coming up with automation idea and developed the tool to automate the reports which saves monthly 12 hours of manual effort.

#### • Insta Awards-Certificate of Appreciation:

For her contribution to GCQIS project. She is a great team player and does her job on time.